wmr.co.th 2017-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Web Perspective Limited

## Privacy Policy

At Web Perspective Ltd (WP), we are dedicated to protecting the privacy and security of your Personal Information (“PI”) you provide us.

Below you will find the updated Privacy Policy for all our web sites, effective December 1st, 2012.

We understand that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part. We take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read the following policy to learn about our privacy practices. By visiting and/or using the services of any of our websites, you are accepting the practices described herein.

We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time and for any reason. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our portfolio of web sites.

Questions regarding this policy should be emailed to [us](mailto:contact@webperspective.hk)

## What Is Private Information (PI)

PI includes any data that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, phone number, or email address.

The PI is regulated, amongst other by the Data Protection Act 1998 and you may request details of personal information which we hold about you at anytime You can review more information about the act here.

## What Information We Collect

In an effort to keep our service as simple and easy to use as possible, we do not create, use or store profiles of our customers. We only record PI and other information which we reasonably consider relevant in conducting business with you.

### We collect your PI each time you submit an enquiry and/or confirm a booking

  * your full name, email address, phone number as and when provided,
  * when collecting funds from you using your credit card, your credit card information, including card number, card type, security number, cardholder name, billing address and expiry date is collected by the secure payment gateway which processes the payment for the accommodation purchased through our site(s),
  * We only add your email address to our mailing distribution list when you elect to do so. This list is used exclusively by us for newsletters and notification of special offers, travel tips, holiday ideas and our company in general.

### When you provide Guest feed back or any user generated content

This is an opt-in option where you may want to leave a feedback on one of our web sites about your experience either with the destination, the property you rented, a restaurants or any other items of your choice. We then collect and store your first name, last name and email address and you agree to transfer the copyright of your feedback to WP.

### Other information we may collect (this is currently not systematic and may happen in the future)

### Statistical information

We record general information about your visit (number of pages viewed, entry & exit pages, …) for statistical purposes. These statistics do not contain any PI.

### IP address

When you visit our site, our web server may automatically records the IP address of your computer (location on the Internet) to assist with fraud protection.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We may use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies via the settings of your web browser. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## How We Use Your Information

We use your PI only for the purpose of responding to and fulfilling your requests for our products and services. Information collected on our site may be used to:

### Purchase of products or services

Information collected when you purchase from us is used by our or the Accommodation Supplier’s online payment gateway to charge your credit card and deliver your booking confirmation electronically. WP never stores directly any information related to your credit card.

We may also use your contact details to reach you about your stay for customer service purposes or to make any changes or cancellations to your booking.

### Send newsletter email

By sending an enquiry and only when selecting unless the dedicated box in the enquiry form, you will receive our regular newsletter.

Our newsletters provide information about the latest deals available, new properties on our portfolio of websites.

WP’s mailing list is not given, sold, or lent to any third party.

If you wish to have your email address removed from WP’s distribution list, you will be able to do so when you receive our next newsletter.

### Communications with you

We will use your email address and/or telephone number to contact you when you submit a question or suggestion or if we have a need to contact you in connection with your booking. We may use your email address and booking information to inform you of additional services and special offers (ie car rental). At your exclusive request, we will immediately refrain from sending any information or offers unrelated to your specific booking.

### Fraud protection

We may pass on your credit card information and IP address to our fraud screening services provider to assist you and us with protecting against fraud.

## Who We Share Your Information With

We do not disclose any information about customer bookings to anyone except in the following circumstances:

### Internal use

We may pass on your personal information to our Customer Service Department for the purposes of assisting with your booking and performing related activities as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Accommodation Suppliers

We provide the guest name for each enquiry made to the relevant Accommodation Supplier. You should be notified within 30 seconds that your enquiry has been send; if you do not, it is likely that your email address was wrongly inserted, we also advise you to check your spam folder. WP also keeps an archive copy as a back-up for the Accommodation Suppliers.

Our Accommodation Suppliers require this information for the booking and may use it if they need to contact you about the booking.

### Payment processing

When payment is made using an online payment gateway, your credit card information and billing address are dealt through the secure payment gateway and the bank which processes your payment. We may pass on your credit card information and IP address (location on the Internet) to our fraud screening service provider.

Other payments may be made with the Accommodation Supplier either via bank transfer or online payment.

We do not maintain a record of any information regarding your credit card details or other banking coordinates.

### Legal obligations

We may be required by law to disclose information you provide to us. We may also disclose information against someone who poses a threat to our interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could cause harm to others.

## How Can You Access And Control Your Information

We believe that site visitors and customers should have control over the collection and use of their PI. Here’s how you can control and have access to your information:

### Subscribe and unsubscribe to our newsletter

You may unsubscribe to our newsletter at any time by using the unsubscribe tool at the bottom of each newsletter you have received

### Booking information

If at any time you would like to alter the PI you provided us in your booking, please send [us](mailto:contact@webperspective.hk) an email with your booking reference number in subject.

### General

If at any time you want to enquire about any of your PI that we store, please email [us](mailto:contact@webperspective.hk).

## How We Protect Your Information

We want you to feel confident about using any of our web sites to plan and purchase your holiday, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect.

While no Web site can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions.

In addition, we use leading security technology and procedures that are regularly reviewed and updated such as encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your exclusive permission or are required by law to do so.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email [us](mailto:contact@webperspective.hk) as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information you found to be incorrect.

## Links To Other Websites

Our website(s) may contain links to other website(s) of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site(s), you should note that we do not have any control over that other website(s).

Therefore, we reject all responsibility for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such site(s) and such site(s) are not governed by this privacy statement.

You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website(s) in question.
